This cake is amazing!
My God, get a room.
I would get a room with this cake.
I think I could show
this cake a good time.
If you had to, what would
you give up, food or sex?
Sex.
Seriously, answer faster.
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
But when she said "sex,"
I wasn't thinking about sex with you.
It's like a giant hug.
Ross, how about you?
Which would you give up?
Food.
How about sex or dinosaurs?
Oh, my God, it's like Sophie's Choice.
Oh, God.
What about you, Joe?
What would you give up, sex or food?
I don't know, it's too hard.
No, you gotta pick one.
Food. No, sex.
Food. Sex. Food. Sex..
I don't know! Oh, God, I want both!
I want.. I want girls on bread!
- You gotta see these pictures of Emma.
- Oh, how cute!
- She looks just like a little doll.
- Oh, no, that is a doll.
Oh, thank God,
because that thing's really creepy.
Look, there's Chandler.
Who's the blond? She's pretty.
He's having an affair.
He is not having an affair!
I'm always right about these things.
No, you're not. Last week,
you thought Ross was trying to kill you.
Well, sorry, but it's hard to believe
that anyone would tell a story that dull..
just to tell it.
There's something going on with them.
Look! He's getting into the car with her.
That doesn't mean anything.
Oh, yeah? Well, let's see.
Okay, duck down.
- Hello?
- Hi, Chandler. It's Phoebe.
I know that Monica is working today..
so I was wondering if you wanted to
come to the movies with me and Rachel.
Oh, I have to work too. Yeah,
I'm stuck here at the office all day.
Well, it's a shame
that you'll miss the movie..
because we were gonna see,
you know, either Liar Liar..
or Betrayal or An Affair to Remember.
Those are all really old.
Okay, then maybe it'll be..
Dude, Where's My Car?
- What?
- They're in a car.
Okay. Well, talk to you later, okay? Bye.
Jeez!
Okay, quick. We gotta find a cab
and follow them.
Yeah, okay. Let me just grab my
night-vision goggles and my stun gun.
I got them.
- Hey.
- Hey. Hi, sweetie.
Hey, you smell like
perfume and cigarettes.
- I was in the car with Nancy.
- Nancy doesn't smoke.
Well, at least the perfume's not mine.
Be thankful for that.
So.. What did you think of the house?
It's everything we've been looking for.
Isn't it? And what about
the amazing wanes coating..
the crown molding
and the dormer windows in the attic?
And the wiggle woms and the zip zorps!
What were the things you said?
- Don't you love the huge yard?
- The fireplace in the bedroom.
And Nancy said it's really underpriced..
because the guy lost his job
and has to move in with his parents!
This is bringing out a lovely color in you.
So do you think we should get it?
I don't know. What do you think?
- I think we should.
- I do too.
This is huge. How bad
do you wanna smoke right now?
I don't know what you mean,
giant, talking cigarette.
Phoebe called as I was getting
into Nancy's car.
If she asks you, I was at work all day.
Got you. When do we tell them?
We don't. Not until it's 100 percent.
Why upset everybody over nothing?
Okay. Right.
- Oh, my God, that is gonna be so hard.
- I know. Good luck with it.
I just can't see Chandler cheating.
I'm telling you guys, we followed
them out to a house in Westchester.
They went in for 45 minutes, and then
they came out looking pretty happy.
Chandler?
Forty-five minutes?
Well, something's not right.
So you went all the way
to Westchester, waited 45 minutes..
- and came back in a cab?
- Yeah.
If each of you guys would like
to pitch in 100 bucks, that would be great.
I can't believe he'd do this to Monica.
I know, and with the baby coming?
- So should we tell her?
- I don't know.
If one of us saw Mike with another
woman, would you want us to tell you?
Why? Who'd you see him with?
- No one. I'm just saying if we did..
- Tell me what you know!
No one! Nothing! Mike's a great guy!
It was hypothetical!
All right. He is a good guy.
You're right. He wouldn't cheat.
If I did see him with someone,
there's no way I..
Who did you see him with?
Oh, look at her. So happy.
If only there were a smaller one
to clean this one.
Hey, is Chandler here?
No, he's picking up dinner.
Why? What's up?
Look, whatever happens,
we're here for you, and we love you.
- All right.
- Chandler might be having an affair.
- What?
- Phoebe and I saw Chandler..
with a blond woman today
outside on the street.
And then we followed them
to a house in Westchester.
They went in together. I'm so sorry.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, that's awful.
What did you think of the house?
What?
Monica, you understand
what we're saying, right?
Yeah. Sure. I mean,
I'm devastated, obviously.
Did you think the neighborhood
was homey?
- Hey.
- You son of a bitch.
Is it me, or have the greetings
gone downhill around here?
Phoebe and Rachel
saw you with Nancy today.
They think you're having an affair.
- Who's Nancy?
- What's going on?
Okay..
All right, you better sit down.
- This is.. This is pretty big.
- Yeah.
I'm not having an affair.
Nancy is our realtor.
I knew he couldn't be
with a woman for 45 minutes!
Why do you have a realtor?
She's been showing
us houses outside of the city.
- What?
- Are you serious?
When we found out
that we were gonna get this baby..
Chandler and I decided
we didn't want to raise a kid in the city.
So you're.. So you're gonna move?
Oh, my God.
Shouldn't we all vote on stuff like this?
What is wrong with raising
a kid in the city?
I'm doing it. Ross is doing it.
Sarah Jessica Parker is doing it!
And that's great for you guys,
but we want a lawn and a swing set.
A street where our kids
can ride their bikes..
and maybe an ice-cream truck
can go by.
So you want to buy a house in the '50s.
Have you thought about
what you're giving up?
You can't move out of the city.
What if..?
What if you want
Chinese food at 5 a.m.?
Or a fake Rolex that breaks
as soon as it rains?
Or an Asian hooker
sent right to your door?
You know what? If you want
to look for a house, that's okay.
No! No, it's not! Don't listen to him.
I'm gonna thump you.
It's okay, because they have
to get it out of their system.
Okay? But you're gonna realize
this is the only place you want to be.
Actually..
we already found a house we love.
- What?
- About an hour ago, we made an offer.
Bet you wish I was
having an affair now, huh?
- You put an offer on a house?
- It's so sweet.
It really is. It has this big yard
that leads down to this stream.
And then there's these old maple trees.
Oh, again with the nature.
What are you, beavers?
Look, I know this is really hard,
and we're really sorry.
Is this because I come over here
without knocking and eat your food?
Because I can stop doing that.
I really, really think I can.
You know that's not the reason, Joe.
I think if you saw it, you'd understand.
You guys were there.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
- Yeah, it is.
- What the hell are you doing?
Well, it is, all right? When we were
out there today, all I kept thinking was:
"I can't believe Chandler's
screwing this woman..
but, man, this would be
a nice place to live!"
Yeah, but so is this.
Yeah. I mean, if you move there,
you have to leave here.
I mean, how can you leave this place?
Come on, Daddy, listen!
All my life, everyone's
always told me, "You're a shoe!"
"You're a shoe! You're a shoe.
You're a shoe!"
I stopped and said,
"What if I don't want to be a shoe?
What if I want to be a purse?
Or a hat?"
I don't want you to buy me a hat,
I..
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
You can see where he'd have trouble.
Well, maybe I'll just stay
here with Monica.
I guess we've established
she's staying with Monica.
Your money's mine, Greene.
Your fly's open, Geller.
You know what I just realized?
"Joker" is "poker" with a "J"!
Coincidence?
That's "joincidence" with a "C"!
Look! Ugly Naked Guy
lit a bunch of candles.
That had to hurt!
Hey, it's your Thanksgiving too.
Instead of watching football,
you could help.
We know.
Rachel, you want to put
the marshmallows in concentric circles.
No, Mon. You want to put them
in concentric circles.
I want to do this.
Every year.
It's stuck!
Step.
How did it get on?
I put it on to scare Chandler.
Oh, my God! Monica's going to
totally freak out!
Plus, it smells really bad in here.
Of course it smells bad.
You have your head up a turkey's ass.
Monica.
Did you get the turkey..?
Oh, my God!
Who is that?
It's Joey.
I got it!
If we win, they have to
get rid of the rooster.
That's interesting!
If you win..
we give up the bird.
But if we win..
we get your apartment.
- Deal!
- What?
"Monica's nickname
when she was a hockey goalie?"
- Big Fat Goalie.
- Correct!
"Rachel claims
it's her favorite movie."
Dangerous Liaisons.
- "Her actual favorite movie is..?"
- Weekend at Bernie's.
"Monica categorizes her towels.
How many categories are there?"
- Everyday use.
- Fancy.
- Guest.
- Fancy guest.
- Two seconds.
- Eleven?
Unbelievable!
Eleven is correct.
"Chandler was how old when he
first touched a girl's breast?"
- 14?
- No, 19.
Thanks, man.
"Joey had an imaginary
childhood friend.
- His name was..?"
- Maurice!
- "His profession was..?"
- Space cowboy!
"What is Chandler Bing's job?"
Ten seconds.
You need this or you lose.
Something to do
with transponding.
He's a transponster!
That's not even a word!
You are mean boys
who are just being mean!
Don't get mad! No one
forced you to raise the stakes.
That is not true!
She forced me!
You got the question wrong.
It was a stupid, unfair question!
Don't blame the questions!
Stop yelling in our apartment!
You are ruining moving day for us.
Chandler!
I saw what you were doing
in the window!
I saw what you're doing to my sister!
Get out here!
Listen, we had a good run.
What was it?
Four, five months?
That's more than most people
have in a lifetime. Goodbye.
Hey, Ross.
What's up, bro?
What the hell are you doing?
What's going on?
I think Ross knows
about me and Monica.
Dude, he's right there.
I thought you were my best friend!
This is my sister!
My best friend and my sister!
I cannot believe this!
We're not just messing around.
I love her.
I'm in love with her.
I'm so sorry that you
had to find out this way.
I'm sorry, but it's true.
I love him too.
My best friend and my sister!
I cannot believe this!
This is the last box of your clothes.
I'm just gonna label it
"What were you thinking?"
I was gonna go across
the hall and write that on Chandler.
Guys, I don't wanna make
things worse, but..
I don't want to live with
Rachel anymore.
You're so mean to each other.
I don't wanna end up like that
with Rachel. I still like you.
That's fine because I'm not moving.
Phoebe, you gotta take her.
I said some bad stuff..
but Rachel has qualities
that make her a good roommate.
She gets tons of catalogs and folds
down the pages of things I'd like.
What else?
When I take a shower..
she leaves me notes on the mirror.
I do. I do do that.
That's nice. I like having things
to read in the bathroom.
When I fall asleep on the couch..
she covers me with a blanket.
Well, you know,
I don't want you to be cold.
And when I told her that I was gonna
move in with Chandler..
she was really supportive.
You were so great.
You made it so easy.
And now you have to leave.
And I have to live with a boy!
- She really left.
- I know.
- Thank you.
- No problem, roomie.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
What the hell is that dog doing here?
A little toast here. Ding, ding!
This isn't exactly the kind of
Thanksgiving you planned..
but for me this has
been really great.
I think because it didn't
involve divorce..
or projectile vomiting.
If you had gone to Vail..
or if you had been with your
family, or if you didn't have..
syphilis and stuff..
we wouldn't be
all together.
So I guess what I'm trying
to say is..
that I'm very thankful that all
of your Thanksgivings sucked.
- That's so sweet!
- Thank you.
Here's to a lousy Christmas!
And a crappy New Year!
- Hear, hear!
You can't move. You just..
You just can't.
Rachel's right.
This is where you guys belong.
You don't wanna live in Westchester.
That's the worst of the Chesters.
You know, sometimes when I'm alone
in my apartment, I look over here..
and you guys are just having dinner..
or watching TV or something..
but it makes me feel better.
And now when I look over,
who am I gonna see?
The Gottliebs? The Yangs?
They don't make me feel so good.
Yeah. So don't move, okay?
Just stay here..
- and maybe close your blinds at night.
- Hey.
Hello?
It's Nancy. They responded to our offer.
And?
Okay. Thanks.
They passed.
They said they won't go a penny
under the asking price.
- We can't afford that.
- I know.
Well, there you go.
I'm really sorry, you guys.
Yeah, I'm sorry too. I'm even more sorry
that phone call didn't come..
before I told you about looking
through the window.
Yeah. Well, we're gonna
let you be alone.
- You gonna be okay?
- Yeah, we'll be okay.
Love you guys.
You know, I'm really sorry
I wasn't more supportive before.
That's okay. We understand.
Yeah, and about this Nancy..
If you're not sleeping with her, should I?
I know there'll be other houses,
but I just..
- I love that one so much.
- Yeah.
Well, it's a good thing we got it then.
- What?
- We got the house.
- Oh, my God.
- I didn't wanna tell you in front of them.
We got it?! We got the house?!
We're getting a house!
- We're getting a house.
- And a baby.
We're growing up.
We sure are.
- Who's gonna tell them?
- Not it!
Not it! Damn it!
Rachel, this is yours.
Why? What are these for?
- You'll see.
- All right, everybody open them.
Wow, this is so beautiful!
These are the ones
I was looking at in the store!
- I know.
- Oh, I love this!
A meatball sub!
Thanks!
Seriously, guys, what's going on?
What are these for?
Well, I didn't know
how to tell you before..
- but we got the house.
- Enjoy!
What did they say?